Finding Aid for the Collection of Awards Ephemera PASC.0209
UCLA Library Special Collections
Collection of awards ephemera
1939-2007
UCLA Library Special Collections
PASC.0209
6.0 Linear Feet (12 boxes)
Awards have honored organizations and individuals in the motion picture and television industry for decades. The collection consists of programs and a small number of printed ephemera items from motion picture and television related award presentation ceremonies, including the Academy Awards, Emmy Awards, American Film Institute Awards, and Golden Globes Awards.
Restrictions on Access
Open for research. All requests to access special collections materials must be made in advance using the request button located on this page.
UCLA Catalog Record ID
UCLA Catalog Record ID: 9950566363606533
Scope and Content
The collection consists of ceremony programs and a small number of printed ephemera items from motion picture and television related award presentation ceremonies. The bulk of the material is from the Academy Awards, Emmy Awards, American Film Institute Awards, and Golden Globes Award presentation ceremonies.
Organization and Arrangement
Arranged in the following series:
Series 1: Academy Awards (Boxes 1-6)
Series 2: American Cinema Awards (Box 10)
Series 3: American Film Institute Life Achievement Awards (Boxes 9-10)
Series 4: Directors Guild Of America Awards (Box 10)
Series 5: Emmy Awards (Boxes 6-8, 11)
Series 6: Emmy Awards (Daytime programming)(Boxes 6)
Series 7: Golden Boot Awards (Box 10)
Series 8: Golden Globe Awards (Boxes 8-9)
Series 9: Television Academy Hall of Fame Awards (Box 10)
Printed ephemera.; Television Awards -- Archives.; Motion pictures -- Awards -- Archives.
- Academy Awards (1939-2007; Boxes 1-6, 12, 14)
  Scope and Contents note
  The bulk of the series consists of ceremony programs from the Academy of Motion Pictures Arts and Sciences, Academy Awards ceremonies. Additionally, there are occasional ballot rules, Governors Ball programs, invitations, luncheon programs and reminder lists related to the award events. The series is arranged chronologically.
  - 11th Annual Academy Awards, 1939 (Box 1)
    General note
    Reminder list of eligible achievements.
  - 12th Annual Academy Awards, 1940 (Box 1)
  - 14th Annual Academy Awards, 1942 (Box 1)
    Reminder list - writing.
  - 15th Annual Academy Awards, 1943 (Box 1)
    Ballot rules.
  - 16th Annual Academy Awards, 1944 (Box 1)
    Ballot rules and reminder list - film.
  - 17th Annual Academy Awards, 1945 (Box 1)
    Ballot rules and reminder list -film.
  - 18th Annual Academy Awards, 1946 (Box 1)
    Reminder list - film.
  - 19th Annual Academy Awards, 1947 (Box 1)
    Ballot rules and ceremony program. Awards bulletin - scientific or technical.
  - 20th Annual Academy Awards, 1948 (Box 1)
    Ceremony program, ephemera and Hollywood Reporter (March 22, 1948).
  - 21st Annual Academy Awards, 1949 (Box 1)
    Ceremony program.
  - 22nd Annual Academy Awards, 1950 (Box 1)
    Ballot rules, ceremony program, screening lists series 13 - 15, complete list of past winners.
  - 23rd Annual Academy Awards, 1951 (Box 1)
    Ballot rules, ceremony program, reminder list - film, screening lists series 17 and 18, and Variety (March 21, 1952).
  - 24th Annual Academy Awards, 1952 (Box 1)
    Ceremony program, reminder list -film, screening lists series 20th - 22nd.
  - 25th Annual Academy Awards, 1953 (Box 1)
    Ceremony program, reminder lists, invitation, Citizen-News (March 20, 1953) and Variety (March 20, 1953).
  - 26th Annual Academy Awards, 1954 (Box 1)
    Ceremony program, reminder list - film, ephemera and scientific or technical awards entries.
  - 27th Annual Academy Awards, 1955 (Box 2)
    Ceremony program, reminder lists, screening list and Variety (March 31, 1955).
  - 28th Annual Academy Awards, 1956 (Box 2)
    Two ceremony programs and reminder lists.
  - 29th Annual Academy Awards, 1957 (Box 2)
    Ceremony program, reminder lists and Citizen News (March 28, 1957).
  - 30th Annual Academy Awards, 1958 (Box 2)
    Ceremony program, reminder lists.
  - 31st Annual Academy Awards, 1959 (Box 2)
    Ballot rules, two ceremony programs, reminder lists, and Citizen News (April 7, 1959).
  - 32nd Annual Academy Awards, 1960 (Box 2)
    Ballot rules, ceremony program, reminder lists and Citizen News (April 5, 1960).
  - 33rd Annual Academy Awards, 1961 (Box 2)
    Ballot rules, ceremony program, reminder list - film, and Citizen News (April 18, 1961).
  - 34th Annual Academy Awards, 1962 (Box 2)
    Ballot rules, ceremony program, reminder list - film, membership list, foreign language film information and Citizen News (April 10, 1962).
  - 35th Annual Academy Awards, 1963 (Box 2)
    Ballot rules, ceremony program, reminder list - film, foreign language film information and past winner list.
  - 36th Annual Academy Awards, 1964 (Box 2)
    Ballot rules, ceremony program and reminder list - film.
  - 37th Annual Academy Awards, 1965 (Box 2)
    Ceremony program, reminder list - film and membership list.
  - 38th Annual Academy Awards, 1966 (Box 3)
    Ballot rules, ceremony program, reminder list - film and membership list.
  - 39th Annual Academy Awards, 1967 (Box 3)
    Ballot rules, ceremony program, reminder list - film and screening list.
  - 40th Annual Academy Awards, 1968 (Box 3)
    Ballot rules, ceremony program, invitation, reminder list - film and membership list.
  - 41st Annual Academy Awards, 1969 (Box 3)
    Ballot rules, ceremony Ceremony program, reminder list - film, past winner list, screening list, The Hollywood Reporter (February 17, 1970) and ephemera.
  - 42nd Annual Academy Awards, 1970 (Box 3)
    Ballot rules, ceremony program, invitation, reminder lists, The Hollywood Reporter (April 8, 1970), Variety (April 8, 1970) and ephemera.
  - 43rd Annual Academy Awards, 1971 (Box 3)
    Ballot rules, ceremony program, invitation, reminder lists, screening list, press kit and ephemera.
  - 44th Annual Academy Awards, 1972 (Box 4)
    Bylaws, ceremony program, invitation, reminder lists, screening list, press kit and ephemera.
  - 45th Annual Academy Awards, 1973 (Box 4)
    Two ceremony programs, invitation, reminder lists and screening list.
  - 46th Annual Academy Awards, 1974 (Box 4)
    Ceremony program, reminder list - film, screening list and press kit.
  - 47th Annual Academy Awards, 1975 (Box 4)
    Ballot rules, ceremony program, invitation, reminder list - film, screening list and ephemera.
  - 48th Annual Academy Awards, 1976 (Box 4)
    Ceremony program, invitation, reminder list - film, screening list and ephemera.
  - 49th Annual Academy Awards, 1977 (Box 4)
    Ballot rules, ceremony program, reminder list - film, screening list and ephemera.
  - 50th Annual Academy Awards, 1978 (Box 4)
    Ballot rules, ceremony program, reminder list - film and academy announcements.
  - 51st Annual Academy Awards, 1979 (Box 5)
    Ceremony program, reminder list - film, screening list, Oscar annual, press kit and ephemera.
  - 52nd Annual Academy Awards, 1980 (Box 5)
  - 53rd Annual Academy Awards, 1981 (Box 5)
    Ballot rules, ceremony program and screening list.
  - 54th Annual Academy Awards, 1982 (Box 5)
    Ceremony program, reminder list - film, luncheon program and ephemera.
  - 55th Annual Academy Awards, 1983 (Box 5)
    Ceremony program and screening list.
  - 56th Annual Academy Awards, 1984 (Box 5)
    Ceremony program, screening list and ASCAP program.
  - 57th Annual Academy Awards, 1985 (Box 5)
    Ceremony program, regulations and ephemera.
  - 58th Annual Academy Awards, 1986 (Box 5)
    Ceremony, luncheon and Governors Ball programs.
  - 59th Annual Academy Awards, 1987 (Box 5)
    Ceremony and luncheon programs.
  - 60th Annual Academy Awards, 1988 (Box 5)
  - 61st Annual Academy Awards, 1989 (Box 5)
  - 62nd Annual Academy Awards, 1990 (Box 5)
  - 62nd Annual Academy Awards, 1990 (Box 12)
    Scope and Content
    Press material.
  - 64th Annual Academy Awards, 1992 (Box 5)
    Luncheon program.
  - 65th Annual Academy Awards, 1993 (Box 5)
  - 66th Annual Academy Awards, 1994 (Box 5)
  - 67th Annual Academy Awards, 1995 (Box 5)
  - 68th Annual Academy Awards, 1996 (Box 5)
  - 69th Annual Academy Awards, 1997 (Box 5)
  - 70th Annual Academy Awards, 1998 (Box 5)
  - 71st Annual Academy Awards, 1999 (Box 5)
    Governors Ball program.
  - 72nd Annual Academy Awards, 2000 (Box 6)
    Ceremony program, news releases and various film photos.
  - 73rd Annual Academy Awards, 2001 (Box 6)
  - 74th Annual Academy Awards, 2002 (Box 6)
    News releases and various film photos.
  - 75th Annual Academy Awards, 2003 (Box 6)
    Ceremony and luncheon programs, Governors Ball invitation, news releases and various film photos.
  - 76th Annual Academy Awards, 2004 (Box 6)
    Luncheon program, Awards programs and Governors Ball invitation.
  - 77th Annual Academy Awards, 2005
    Program and invitation and nominees luncheon iprogram and invitation.
  - 78th Annual Academy Awards, 2006 (Box 14)
    Ceremony program, invitation, tickets and souvenir booklet (2 copies); and luncheon invitation and program.
  - 79th Annual Academy Awards, 2007 (Box 14)
    Program and souvenir booket; and invitation to luncheon.
  - Posters, 1996, 1978-1980, 1982-1984, 1986, 1993-1995, 1997, 2000-2003 (Box 13)
- American Cinema Awards (1985, 1989; Boxes 10, 12)
  The series consists of programs for American Cinema Awards ceremony presentation.
  - 3rd Annual American Cinema Awards - Honoring Deborah Kerr and Roddy McDowall, 1985 (Box 10)
  - 6th Annual American Cinema Awards - Honoring Betty Davis, Clint Easwookd, and Julio Iglesias, 1989 (Box 12)
    Press release and Foundation publicity.
- American Film Institute Life Achievement Awards (1974-1992, 1999, 2001; Boxes 9-10, 12)
  The series consists of programs from the American Film Institute Life Achievement Award's ceremony presentations. The series is arranged chronologically.
  - 2nd Annual American Film Institute Life Achievement Awards - A Salute to James Cagney, 1974 (Box 11)
  - 3rd Annual American Film Institute Life Achievement Awards - A Salute to Orson Welles, 1975 (Box 11)
  - 5th Annual American Film Institute Life Achievement Awards - A Salute to Bette Davis, 1977 (Box 11)
  - 6th Annual American Film Institute Life Achievement Award - A Salute to Henry Fonda, 1978 (Box 9)
  - 7th Annual American Film Institute Life Achievement Award - A Salute to Alfred Hitchcock, 1979 (Box 9)
  - 8th Annual American Film Institute Life Achievement Award - A Salute to James Stewart, 1980 (Box 9)
  - 9th Annual American Film Institute Life Achievement Award - A Salute to Fred Astaire, 1981 (Box 9)
  - 10th Annual American Film Institute Life Achievement Award - A Salute to Henry Fonda, 1982 (Box 9)
  - 14th Annual American Film Institute Life Achievement Award - A Salute to Billy Wilder, 1986 (Box 9)
  - 15th Annual American Film Institute Life Achievement Award - A Salute to Barbara Stanwyck, 1987 (Box 9)
  - 16th Annual American Film Institute Life Achievement Award - A Salute to Jack Lemmon, 1988 (Box 9)
  - 17th Annual American Film Institute Life Achievemnet Award - A Salute to Gregory Peck, 1989 (Box 9)
  - 18th Annual American Film Institute Life Achievement Award - A Salute to David Lean, 1990 (Box 9)
  - 19th Annual American Film Institute Life Achievement Award - A Salute to Kirk Douglas, 1991 (Box 10)
  - 20th Annual American Film Institute Life Achievement Award - A Salute to Sidney Poitier, 1992 (Box 10)
  - 27th Annual American Film Institute Life Achievement Award - Honoring Dustin Hoffman, 1999 (Box 12)
  - 29th Annual American Film Institute Life Achievement Award - A Salute to Barbra Streisand, 2001 (Box 10)
- Directors Guild of America Awards (1986-1989, 1992, 1994; Boxes 10, 12)
  The series consists of ceremony programs for the annual Directors Guild of America Award presentations. The series is arranged chronologically.
  - 38th Annual Directors Guild Of America Awards, 1986 (Box 12)
    Program and press material.
  - 39th Annual Directors Guild Of America Awards, 1987 (Box 12)
    Program, ticket and press material.
  - 44th Annual Directors Guild Of America Awards, 1992
  - 40th Annual Directors Guild Of America Awards, 1988 (Box 10)
  - 41st Annual Directors Guild Of America Awards, 1989 (Box 10)
  - 44th Annual Directors Guild Of America Awards, 1992 (Box 12)
    Program.
  - 46th Annual Directors Guild Of America Awards, 1994 (Box 12)
- Emmy Awards (1952-1995, 1998; Boxes 6-8, 11, 12)
  The series consists of ceremony programs from the annual Emmy Awards presentation ceremonies. The series is arranged chronologically.
  - 4th Annual Emmy Awards, 1952 (Box 6)
  - 7th Annual Emmy Awards, 1954 (Box 6)
  - 8th Annual Emmy Awards, 1955 (Box 11)
  - 9th Annual Emmy Awards, 1956 (Box 11)
  - 10th Annual Emmy Awards, 1958 (Box 6)
  - 11th Annual Emmy Awards, 1959 (Box 6)
  - 12th Annual Emmy Awards, 1960 (Box 6)
    Ceremony program, reminder list and clippings.
  - 13th Annual Emmy Awards, 1961 (Box 6)
    Ceremony program and reminder list.
  - 14th Annual Emmy Awards, 1962 (Box 7)
  - 15th Annual Emmy Awards, 1963 (Box 7)
  - 16th Annual Emmy Awards, 1964 (Box 7)
  - 17th Annual Emmy Awards, 1965 (Box 7)
  - 18th Annual Emmy Awards, 1966 (Box 7)
    Ceremony program and standardized constitution of chapters.
  - 19th Annual Emmy Awards, 1967 (Box 7)
  - 20th Annual Emmy Awards, 1968 (Box 7)
  - 21st Annual Emmy Awards, 1969 (Box 7)
  - 23nd Annual Emmy Awards, 1971 (Box 7)
  - 24th Annual Emmy Awards, 1972 (Box 7)
  - 25th Annual Emmy Awards, 1973 (Box 7)
  - 26th Annual Emmy Awards (1st daytime programming), 1974 (Box 7)
    Ceremony program, press kit and show notes.
  - 27th Annual Emmy Awards (2nd daytime programming), 1975 (Box 7)
  - 28th Annual Emmy Awards, 1976 (Box 7)
  - 28th Annual Emmy Awards script, 1976 May (Box 12)
  - 29th Annual Emmy Awards, 1977 (Box 7)
  - 29th Annual Emmy Awards script, 1977 Sept (Box 12)
  - 30th Annual Emmy Awards, 1978 (Box 7)
  - 31th Annual Emmy Awards, 1979 (Box 7)
  - 32nd Annual Emmy Awards, 1980 (Box 7)
  - 33rd Annual Emmy Awards, 1981 (Box 7)
  - 34th Annual Emmy Awards, 1982 (Box 7)
  - 35th Annual Emmy Awards, 1983 (Box 7)
  - 36th Annual Emmy Awards, 1984 (Box 7)
  - 37th Annual Emmy Awards, 1985 (Box 7)
  - 38th Annual Emmy Awards, 1986 (Box 7)
  - 39th Annual Emmy Awards, 1987 (Box 8)
  - 40th Annual Emmy Awards, 1988 (Box 8)
  - 41st Annual Emmy Awards, 1989 (Box 8)
    Ceremony program and press kit.
  - 43rd Annual Emmy Awards, 1991 (Box 8)
  - 44th Annual Emmy Awards, 1992 (Box 8)
  - 45th Annual Emmy Awards, 1993 (Box 8)
  - 46th Annual Emmy Awards, 1994 (Box 8)
  - 49th Annual Emmy Awards, 1995 (Box 8)
  - 50th Annual Emmy Awards, 1998 (Box 12)
  - Posters, 1987, 1998 (Box 13)
- Emmy Awards (Daytime programming) (1974-1977; Boxes 6)
  The series consists of programs from the annual Emmy Awards presentation ceremonies. The series is arranged chronologically. See also Emmy Awards.
  - 3rd Annual Emmy Awards, 1976 (Box 6)
  - 4th Annual Emmy Awards, 1977 (Box 6)
- Emmy Awards - daytime programming
  The series consists of programs from the Emmy Awards' (Daytime programming) presentation ceremonies. The series is arranged chronologically.
  - 1st Annual Emmy Awards, 1974 (Box 6)
  - 2nd Annual Emmy Awards, 1975 (Box 6)
- Golden Boot Awards (1989; Box 10)
  The series consists of one ceremony programs for the 7th annual Golden Boot Awards.
  - 7th Annual Golden Boot Awards, 1989 (Box 10)
- Golden Globe Awards (1960, 1972-2004; Boxes 8-9)
  The The series consists of programs from the annual Golden Globe Awards' presentation ceremonies. The series is arranged chronologically.
  - 17th Annual Golden Globe Awards, 1960 (Box 8)
  - 29th Annual Golden Globe Awards, 1972 (Box 8)
  - 30th Annual Golden Globe Awards, 1973 (Box 8)
  - 31st Annual Golden Globe Awards, 1974 (Box 8)
  - 32nd Annual Golden Globe Awards, 1975 (Box 8)
  - 33rd Annual Golden Globe Awards, 1976 (Box 8)
    Ceremony program
  - 34th Annual Golden Globe Awards, 1977 (Box 8)
  - 35th Annual Golden Globe Awards, 1978 (Box 8)
  - 36th Annual Golden Globe Awards, 1979 (Box 8)
  - 37th Annual Golden Globe Awards, 1980 (Box 8)
  - 38th Annual Golden Globe Awards, 1981 (Box 8)
  - 39th Annual Golden Globe Awards, 1982 (Box 8)
  - 40th Annual Golden Globe Awards, 1983 (Box 8)
  - 41st Annual Golden Globe Awards, 1984 (Box 8)
  - 42nd Annual Golden Globe Awards, 1985 (Box 8)
  - 43rd Annual Golden Globe Awards, 1986 (Box 8)
  - 44th Annual Golden Globe Awards, 1987 (Box 8)
  - 45th Annual Golden Globe Awards, 1988 (Box 8)
  - 46th Annual Golden Globe Awards, 1989 (Box 8)
  - 47th Annual Golden Globe Awards, 1990 (Box 8)
  - 48th Annual Golden Globe Awards, 1991 (Box 8)
  - 49th Annual Golden Globe Awards, 1992 (Box 8)
  - 50th Annual Golden Globe Awards, 1993 (Box 8)
  - 51st Annual Golden Globe Awards, 1994 (Box 9)
  - 52nd Annual Golden Globe Awards, 1995 (Box 9)
  - 53rd Annual Golden Globe Awards, 1996 (Box 9)
  - 54th Annual Golden Globe Awards, 1997 (Box 9)
  - 55th Annual Golden Globe Awards, 1998 (Box 9)
  - 56th Annual Golden Globe Awards, 1999 (Box 9)
  - 58th Annual Golden Globe Awards, 2001 (Box 9)
  - 59th Annual Golden Globe Awards, 2002 (Box 9)
    Ceremony program and photographs.
  - 60th Annual Golden Globe Awards, 2003 (Box 9)
  - 61st Annual Golden Globe Awards, 2004 (Box 9)
    Ceremony program and past winners.
- Television Academy Hall of Fame Awards (1985-1996; Box 10, 12)
  The series consists of programs from the Television Academy Hall of Fame Award's presentation ceremonies. The series is arranged chronologically.
  - 2nd Annual Television Academy Hall of Fame Awards, 1985 (Box 10)
  - 4th Annual Television Academy Hall of Fame Awards, 1987 (Box 10)
  - 7th Annual Television Academy Hall of Fame Awards, 1990 (Box 10)
  - 11th Annual Television Academy Hall of Fame Awards, 1994 (Box 10)
  - 13th Annual Television Academy Hall of Fame Awards, 1996 (Box 10)
- Women of the Motion Picture Industry (1974; Box 12)
  Program representing the Women of the Motion Picture Industry (WOMPI) awards.
  - 12th Annual Women of the Motion Picture Industry Installation and Awards Dinner Dance program, 1974 (Box 12)